Hi, this is Jeremy Howard, and you're listening to Coffee Time Data Science, a podcast for data science enthusiasts, where I interview practitioners, researchers, and Kagglers about their journey, experience, and talk all things data science.
And before we begin, I apologize for the change to our schedule.
Of course, usually you would be seeing Chai Time Data Science on this channel with Sanyam Bhutani.
Unfortunately, he's not available today.
He had a prior appointment on another podcast, and he was not able to join Chai Time Data Science.
We hope you enjoy this special episode of Coffee Time Data Science.
And without further ado, I would like to invite our very special VIP guest, newly anointed Kaggle Grand Master, Sanyam Bhutani.
Sanyam, welcome to Coffee Time Data Science.
Thank you, Jeremy.
Usually, I'm very anti coffee, but I'll have to allow that.
I still can't believe you weren't kidding.
And I mentioned in our message also, like I, I think I don't deserve this.
But thank you.